{"data":[{"question":"Caricature, a type of comic exaggeration, is common used in political cartoons.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"type of","b":"exaggeration","c":"common","d":"in","answer":"3","explain":" - Common-> commonly","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"One and more sentences related to the same topic form a paragraph.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"and","b":"related to","c":"same","d":"form","answer":"1","explain":" - And->or","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Mirrors done of shiny metal were used by the Egyptians in ancient times.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"done","b":"were used","c":"in","d":"times","answer":"1","explain":" - Done->made","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Mark Twain's Adventures of Huckleberry Finn are one of America's national treasures.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are","b":"of","c":"national","d":"treasures","answer":"1","explain":" - Are-> is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"In his early days as a direct, Charlie Chaplin produced 62 short silent comedy films in four years.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"his","b":"direct","c":"short silent","d":"in four","answer":"2","explain":" - Direct-> director","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Some studies show that young babies prefer the smell of milk to those of other liquids.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"that young babies","b":"smell","c":"those","d":"liquids","answer":"3","explain":" - Those-> that","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Plants absorb water and nutrients and anchoring themselves in the soil with their roots.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"absorb water","b":"anchoring themselves","c":"the soil","d":"their roots","answer":"2","explain":" - Anchoring themselves-> anchor themselves","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"To understand the directions, they must be read carefully.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"To understand","b":"the","c":"they must be read","d":"carefully","answer":"3","explain":" - Must be read-> must read","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"The children were surprised when the teacher had them to close their books unexpectedly.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"were surprised","b":"when","c":"to close","d":"unexpectedly","answer":"3","explain":" - To close-> close","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Sitting alone in his room, the strange noise frightened him.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Sitting","b":"in","c":"his","d":"the strange noise frightened him","answer":"4","explain":" - the strange noise frightened him-> he was frightened by the strange noise","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"}]}